<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="bagikan_hasil">The conversion result from %1$s %2$s to %3$s is %4$s</string>
    <string name="pilih">Select</string>
    <string name="app_name">Conversion App</string>
    <string name="hasil">Result: %1$s</string>
    <string name="input_invalid">Cannot be empty.</string>
    <string name="kembali">Back</string>
    <string name="bagikan">Share</string>
    <string name="judul_suhu">Temperature Conversion</string>
    <string name="judul_panjang">Length Conversion</string>
    <string name="judul_berat">Weight Conversion</string>
    <string name="konversi">Convert</string>
    <string name="des_suhu">Temperature</string>
    <string name="des_panjang">Length</string>
    <string name="des_berat">Weight</string>
    <string name="dropdown">Dropdown Icon</string>
    <string name="convert">Convert</string>
    <string name="input_suhu">Input temperature</string>
    <string name="input_panjang">Input lenght</string>
    <string name="input_berat">Input weight</string>
    <string name="copyright_suhu">This Conversion App was developed as an educational tool to help users convert values between units such as temperature, length, and weight.\n\nThe temperature conversion feature allows you to quickly and accurately convert between Celsius, Fahrenheit, and Kelvin.\n\nThe app is designed with a simple and user-friendly interface, ideal for students, teachers, and the general public.\n\nDeveloped by Faris Rizky Ramadhan as part of a mobile programming learning project.\n\nCopyright © 2025.</string>
    <string name="tentang_suhu">About Temperature Conversion</string>
    <string name="copyright_panjang">This Conversion App provides a length unit conversion feature to help users calculate values between units such as millimeters, centimeters, meters, kilometers, inches, feet, and miles.\n\nThe length conversion feature is designed to be easy to use and deliver accurate results quickly.\n\nThis app is very useful for students, engineers, and anyone who needs a practical length measurement tool.\n\nDeveloped by Faris Rizky Ramadhan as part of a mobile programming learning project.\n\nCopyright © 2025. All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="tentang_panjang">About Lenght Conversion</string>
    <string name="copyright_berat">This Conversion App also supports weight unit conversion to help users calculate values between units such as milligrams, grams, kilograms, tons, ounces, and pounds.\n\nThe weight conversion feature is designed with an intuitive interface and provides fast results.\n\nIt is ideal for use in learning, cooking, logistics, or any other activity involving weight units.\n\nDeveloped by Faris Rizky Ramadhan as part of a mobile programming learning project.\n\nCopyright © 2025. All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="tentang_berat">About Weight Conversion</string>
</resources>